一旦你学习了怎样解析 JSON 数据，那么就非常
Once you've learned how to parse JSON data, it's pretty
直观地能够解析余下
straight forward to be able to parse the rest of the
我们需要的字段。因为这并不是一个Java或JSON
fields that we need. Since this isn't a course on
的课程，我们将在下面的gist中提供
Java or JSON, we're going to provide you with the parsing
解析的代码。这就是gist的样子。
code in the gist below. And this is what the
共有三个辅助方法。第一个是
gist looks like. There are three helper methods. The first is
格式化日期。第二个是格式化最高和最低温度字符串的。第三个是
for formatting dates. The second is for rounding temperatures. The third
将返回的JSON字符串转化成天气预报的自定义格式字符串的数组。
is for turning a forecastJsonStr, into an array of weather forecasts.
更新FetchWeatherTask使用这些辅助方法。并且
Update the Fetch Weather Tasks to use these helpful functions. And
在doInBackground()方法中应该返回一个天气预报的字符串数组。
the do in background method should return a string array of
你应该输出日志去检查数组是不是
forecasts. You can log the output to check that the array
正确。每天的天气预报的格式应该看起来像这样。
is correct. The format of one day's forecast should look like this.